直方图归一化是一种常用技术，用于增强其中的细节
Histogram normalization is a common technique that is used to enhance fine detail within
一个图像。
an image.
从图像强度直方图计算累积直方图。
The cumulative histogram is computed from the image intensity histogram.
累积直方图中的每列被计算为所有图像强度的总和
Each column in the cumulative histogram is computed as the sum of all the image intensity
直方图值高达并包括该灰度级，然后按比例缩放
histogram values up to and including that grey level, and then it is scaled so that
最终值为1.0。
the final value is 1.0.
你会注意到的累积直方图是它在非常陡峭的时候
And what you will notice with the cumulative histogram is that it is very steep when the
输入直方图非常大，当输入直方图相当时它是相当平坦的
input histogram is quite large, and it is fairly flat when the input histogram is quite
低。
low.
因此，我们可以在这里看到累积直方图快速增长的几个领域。
So we can see here a couple of areas where the cumulative histogram has grown quite quickly.
现在我们使用累积直方图作为映射。
Now we use the cumulative histogram as a mapping.
因此对于每个输入值，以及0到255范围内的这些无符号整数像素值，
So for every input value, and these unsigned integer pixel values in the range 0 to 255,
我取一个输入像素x，然后通过累积直方图对其进行映射，得到结果。
I take an input pixel x and I map it through the cumulative histogram and I get the result.
所以我的x函数是通过图像的累积直方图的非线性映射。
So my function of x is a non-linear mapping through the cumulative histogram of the image.
因此，蒙娜丽莎图像的结果是增强了许多细节。
So the result of this on the Mona Lisa image is to enhance a lot of the fine detail.
因此，如果我们看一下背景，我们可以看到它在相当暗的区域
So if we have a look into the background we can see areas where it is fairly dark in the
原始图像和直方图归一化增加了局部对比度;做好了
original image and where the histogram normalization has increased the local contrast; made it
我们可以看到细节，否则我们在输入中很难看到
possible for us to see detail that otherwise we could not see very easily in the input
图片。
image.
这是monadic图像处理操作的另一个例子。
This is another example of a monadic image processing operation.